it is thanks I appreciate it
welcome extra fight this time I know our
side will win
you ready you son yes I'm ready
firing
got a hurry you missed that plane
you
well I was right you are a
sentimentalist stay where you are
I don't know what you're talking about
but you just did for Laszlo that fairy
tale you invented to send he'll sew away
with him I know a little about women my
friend she went but she knew you were
lying anyway thanks for helping me out
I suppose you know this isn't going to
be very pleasant for either of us
especially for you I'll have to arrest
you of course as soon as the plane goes
Louie what was the meaning of that phone
call Victor Laszlo is on that plane why
do you stand here why don't you stop him
ask mr. Rick
in a wave Nashville I would advise you
not to interfere I was willing to shoot
captain Renault and I'm willing to shoot
you
you know put that phone down get me the
right guitar put it down
major stars has been shot
round up the usual suspects
my Nexus what do you
well Rick you're not only a
sentimentalist but you become a patriot
maybe but it seemed like a good time to
start
I think perhaps our right
it might be a good idea for you to
disappear from Casablanca for a while
there's a free French garrison over a
browser view I could be induced to
arrange a passage my letter of transit I
could use a trip it hasn't made it if
it's about our bet she's still only ten
thousand francs and that ten thousand
francs should pay our expenses our
expenses Louie I think this is the
beginning of a beautiful friendship
you